<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Giacomo Lenzini</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Giacomo Lenzini</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.145.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spatial VDP: How I Rocked-Boosted a NASA XSS from P5 to P2 🚀</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/nasa-vdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/nasa-vdp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few months ago, I read an intriguing &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.keephack.ing/2025-02-17-Houston-We-Have-a-vulnerability/&#34;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; by Valerio &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;MrSaighnal&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rdquo; Alessandroni, detailing how he earned a &lt;strong&gt;letter of acknowledgment from NASA&lt;/strong&gt; for reporting a vulnerability. That story stuck with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NASA&amp;rsquo;s Vulnerability Disclosure Program (VDP)&lt;/strong&gt; is a non-monetary initiative that invites security researchers to report vulnerabilities in NASA&amp;rsquo;s public-facing systems. Unlike traditional bug bounties, the reward is purely ethical hacking glory – but with a cosmic twist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For valid P3 or higher vulnerabilities, researchers receive:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/whoami/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;who-am-i&#34;&gt;Who am i&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a 24-year-old guy graduate in cybersecurity, currently working as an &lt;strong&gt;Offensive Security Specialist&lt;/strong&gt;. In my role, I perform various types of penetration tests to strengthen the security posture of organizations. In my spare time, I actively participate in &lt;strong&gt;Bug Bounty&lt;/strong&gt; programs and engage in Capture The Flag (CTF) challenges and practice on various vulnerable labs (HackTheBox) to enhance my skills in ethical hacking and red teaming. I am also passionate about sports, having practiced kickboxing for 13 years, including 10 years at a competitive level. Currently, I practice CrossFit to maintain my fitness and discipline.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
